Guide to the William C. Bullitt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1882-1967; Series I
  - Morlock, George A., 1934-1941 (Box 59, Folder 1450)
  - Morris, Constance Lily, 1919, 1933-1940 (Box 59, Folder 1451)
  - Morris, David H., 1933-1943 (Box 59, Folder 1452 - 1457)
  - Morris, Ira Nelson, 1919-1933 (Box 59, Folder 1458)
  - Morris, Robert, 1945-1952 (Box 59, Folder 1459)
  - Morrison, Bernard, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 1460)
  - Morrison, Ralph W., 1933-1947 (Box 59, Folder 1461)
  - Moses, George H., 1933-1943 (Box 59, Folder 1462)
  - Mowrer, Edgar A., 1933-1934, undated (Box 59, Folder 1463)
  - Mowrer, Lilian, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 1464)
  - Mullen, J. Arthur, 1933-1934 (Box 59, Folder 1465)
  - Mundt, Karl, 1946-1954 (Box 59, Folder 1466)
  - Munson, Charles, 1948-1954 (Box 59, Folder 1467)
  - Murphy, Charles A., 1933-1940 (Box 60, Folder 1468 - 1470)
  - Murphy, Ray, 1938-1943 (Box 60, Folder 1471)
  - Murphy, Robert D., 1934-1966, undated (Box 60, Folder 1472 - 1475)
    See also: Oversize Folder 35
  - Murphy, Vincent, 1933-1944 (Box 60, Folder 1476 - 1477)
  - Murray, Lee, 1940-1944 (Box 60, Folder 1478)
  - Murray, Robert H., 1941 (Box 60, Folder 1479)
  - Murray, Wallace [includes photographs], 1933-1938 (Box 60, Folder 1480)
  - N (Box 61, Folder 1481 - 1488)
  - Narodny, Ivan [includes photographs], 1933-1951 (Box 61, Folder 1489)
  - National Committee on the Housing Emergency, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 61, Folder 1490)
  - National Press Club, 1933-1940 (Box 61, Folder 1491)
  - Neal, C. Lloyd, 1934 (Box 61, Folder 1492)
  - Neeser, Robert W., 1936-1940 (Box 61, Folder 1493)
  - Neff, Elizabeth, 1934-1938 (Box 61, Folder 1494)
  - Neprud, Carl, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 1495)
  - Nesbitt, Dorothy Easton, 1939-1941, 1944 (Box 61, Folder 1496)
  - Netanyahu, B., 1943-1944 (Box 61, Folder 1497)
  - Nettleton family, 1939-1953 (Box 61, Folder 1498)
  - Neuhausen, Nellie, 1939-1944 (Box 61, Folder 1499)
  - Neumann, Emanuel, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 1500)
  - Neumann, Robert G., 1940-1941 (Box 61, Folder 1501)
  - Neveu, Pie-Eugène, 1936-1940 (Box 61, Folder 1502)
  - Newell, Gertrude F., 1934-1940 (Box 61, Folder 1503)
  - Nicholas, Earl, 1940-1943 (Box 62, Folder 1504 - 1506)
  - Nicholl, Helen R., 1940-1941 (Box 62, Folder 1507)
  - Nicolls, Moyra, 1954-1956, 1658-1962, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 1508)
  - Nimmer, D. R., 1934-1939 (Box 62, Folder 1509)
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous and family, 1952-1963, 1967, undated (Box 62, Folder 1510)
  - Noble, George Bernard, 1919, 1933-1953 (Box 62, Folder 1511)
  - Nogga, Phillip, 1940 (Box 62, Folder 1512)
  - Noland, Augusta Clark, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 1513)
  - Nonnenmacher, Nicholas T., 1950-1954 (Box 62, Folder 1514)
  - Nowell, Virginia, 1941-1942, undated (Box 62, Folder 1515)
  - O (Box 62, Folder 1516 - 1519)
  - Oakley, Thornton, 1935, 1943-1944 (Box 62, Folder 1520)
  - O'Brien, John A., 1948-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1521)
  - O'Brien, John J., 1933-1956 (Box 62, Folder 1522)
  - O'Brien, William O., 1940-1942 (Box 62, Folder 1523)
  - O'Connell, Ambrose, 1933-1938 (Box 62, Folder 1524)
  - O'Connor, Basil, 1933-1942 (Box 62, Folder 1525)
  - O'Conor, Herbert R., 1949 (Box 62, Folder 1526)
  - O'Donnell, Doris Fleeson and John H., 1933-1943 (Box 62, Folder 1527)
  - Office International du Vin, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 1528 - 1530)
  - Offie, Carmel, 1934-1936, 1940-1947, 1951-1964 (Box 63, Folder 1531 - 1536)
  - Ogburn, Charles, Jr., 1946 (Box 63, Folder 1537)
  - Ogden, Charles K., 1933 (Box 63, Folder 1538)
  - O'Keefe, Jerome, 1948-1949 (Box 63, Folder 1539)
  - Olivier, Marcel, 1937-1941 (Box 63, Folder 1540)
  - Onderdonk, Frances Skillman, 1940 (Box 63, Folder 1541)
  - Opfer, Ivan [includes drawing], 1943-1944 (Box 63, Folder 1542)
  - Orbay, H. Rauf [includes photographs], 1946-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1543)
  - Ordynski, Richard, 1940 (Box 63, Folder 1544)
  - Ormandy, Eugene, 1937-1951 (Box 63, Folder 1545)
  - Osborne, Lithgow, 1918, 1934-1941 (Box 63, Folder 1546)
  - Osler, William, 1914, 1915, undated (Box 63, Folder 1547)
  - Ostroff, Isidor, 1942 (Box 63, Folder 1548)
  - Osusky, Stefan, 1937-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1549 - 1550)
  - Ottinger, Henri, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 1551)
  - Otto, Archduke of Austria, 1939-1951 (Box 63, Folder 1552)
  - P (Box 64, Folder 1553 - 1572)
  - Packard, Austin G., 1939-1946 (Box 64, Folder 1573)
  - Packer, Earl and Iris, 1939-1943 (Box 64, Folder 1574)
  - Packlen, W., 1948 (Box 64, Folder 1575)
  - Page, Ralph W., 1941-1943 (Box 64, Folder 1576)
  - Pai Shiu Chuan, 1944-1950, 1952-1958, 1963-1964, undated (Box 65, Folder 1577 - 1579)
  - Paine, Diana B., 1941-1943 (Box 65, Folder 1580)
  - Palmer, C. F., 1934-1942 (Box 65, Folder 1581)
  - Palmer, Ernest, Jr., 1940 (Box 65, Folder 1582)
  - Palmer, Paul, 1948-1952, undated (Box 65, Folder 1583)
  - Palmer, Peggy, 1952-1954 (Box 65, Folder 1584)
  - Palyi, Melchior, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 1585)
  - Pan American Airways, 1940-1963 (Box 65, Folder 1586)
    See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 2113
  - Pangborn, Clifford and Marjorie, 1934-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1587)
  - Parker, George Lawrence, 1933 (Box 65, Folder 1588)
  - Partridge, Stanley, 1941-1942 (Box 65, Folder 1589)
  - Pathe, A. L. C., 1941 (Box 65, Folder 1590)
  - Patterson, Alexander E., 1941-1948 (Box 65, Folder 1591)
  - Patterson, Eleanor Medill "Cissy", 1933-1948, undated (Box 65, Folder 1592)
  - Patterson, George Stuart, 1941-1942 (Box 65, Folder 1593)
  - Patterson, Jefferson, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 1594)
  - Patterson, Jere, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 1595)
  - Patterson, Margaret, 1941-1946 (Box 65, Folder 1596)
  - Patterson, Robert P., 1933-1947, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 1597)
  - Patzert, Rudolph, 1934 (Box 65, Folder 1598)
  - Paul, Florence S., 1933-1941 (Box 65, Folder 1599)
  - Paul-Cavallier, Marcel, 1938-1939 (Box 65, Folder 1600)
  - Pavlov, Ivan Petrovich, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 1601)
  - Paxton, Ann, 1947-1952 (Box 65, Folder 1602)
  - Payer, Harry F., 1933-1943 (Box 65, Folder 1603)
  - Peacock, Sam C., 1947 (Box 65, Folder 1604)
  - Pearson, Drew, 1933-1942 (Box 65, Folder 1605)
  - Pease, Howard H., 1933-1954 (Box 65, Folder 1606)
  - Pease, Roger W., 1940 (Box 65, Folder 1607)
  - Peck, Willys R., 1934-1935 (Box 65, Folder 1608)
  - Pee, Peter T. K., 1947-1950 (Box 65, Folder 1609)
  - Pei, Tsuyee [includes photographs], 1947-1957 (Box 65, Folder 1610 - 1611)
  - Pell, Herbert C., 1939-1941, undated (Box 65, Folder 1612)
  - Penfield, Marshal, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 1613)
  - Pennsylvania Museum of Art, 1937 (Box 66, Folder 1614)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1948-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1615)
  - Pepper, O. H. Perry and Lalite, 1940-1962 (Box 66, Folder 1616)
  - Perkins, Frances, 1934-1939 (Box 66, Folder 1617)
  - Perkins, Malone and Washburn, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 1618)
  - Perkins, Milo, 1941-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1619)
  - Perlman, Philip B., 1949-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1620)
  - Perry, E. H., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 1621)
  - Pershing, John J., 1937-1944 (Box 66, Folder 1622)
  - Peters, Myrtle D., 1947 (Box 66, Folder 1623)
  - Peters, W. A., Jr., 1933-1946 (Box 66, Folder 1624)
  - Pettit, Walter W., 1919, 1933-1938, undated (Box 66, Folder 1625)
  - Pew, Joseph Newton, Jr., 1941 (Box 66, Folder 1626)
  - Pfeiffer, Forest D., 1942-1948 (Box 66, Folder 1627)
  - Pfeiffer, Gustavus A., 1940 (Box 66, Folder 1628)
  - Pflieger, Robert P., 1941-1942 (Box 66, Folder 1629)
  - Phillips, Caroline D., 1933-1942 (Box 66, Folder 1630)
  - Phillips, William, 1933-1943, undated (Box 66, Folder 1631 - 1632)
  - Phipps, Eric, 1932, 1940-1942 (Box 66, Folder 1633)
  - Phipps, Frances and Mary, 1937-1939 (Box 66, Folder 1634)
  - Pierce, L. F., 1933-1940 (Box 66, Folder 1635)
  - Pierson, Warren Lee, 1939-1941, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 1636)
  - Pieve, Ida R., 1940 (Box 66, Folder 1637)
  - Pigman, Augustus, 1941 (Box 66, Folder 1638)
  - Pinchot, Cornelia Bryce, 1920, 1925, 1940-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1639)
  - Pinkava, J. [includes photographs], 1938 (Box 66, Folder 1640)
  - Pitcairn Island Radio Station, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 1641)
  - Planiol, René, 1941-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1642)
  - Platt, Philip S., 1910-1914, 1918, 1933-1947, 1966, undated (Box 66, Folder 1643)
  - Platt, Yungman, and Company, 1920-1925, 1941-1945, 1947-1962 (Box 66, Folder 1644 - 1648)
    See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 613
  - Pleven, Anne René, 1936-1941, 1944, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 1649)
  - Pleven, René, 1933-1941, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 1650)
  - Plitt, Edwin A., 1938-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1651)
  - Polish American Congress, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 66, Folder 1652)
  - Polk, Frank L., 1918, 1933-1942 (Box 66, Folder 1653)
  - Pollack, Herbert, 1954-1956, undated (Box 67, Folder 1654)
  - Pollard, Alice, 1948 (Box 67, Folder 1655)
  - Pollatts-Pascalides, George A. [includes photographs], 1917-1918, 1933-1934 (Box 67, Folder 1656)
  - Pommery and Greno, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 1657)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham, 1933, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 1658)
  - Porterfield, Laura Lee, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 1659)
  - Pouritch, Bojidar, 1943-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1660)
  - Pouyer, Jean, 1937-1946 (Box 67, Folder 1661)
  - Powell, Diana Kearny, 1940-1942 (Box 67, Folder 1662)
  - Powell, P. P., 1940-1942 (Box 67, Folder 1663)
  - Pratt, Edward Ewing, 1933-1944 (Box 67, Folder 1664)
  - Premier Rayon Review, 1934 (Box 67, Folder 1665)
  - Prendergast, George Anthony Edward, 1938-1954 (Box 67, Folder 1666)
  - Preugschat, Richard, 1935-1940 (Box 67, Folder 1667)
  - Price, E. Melville, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 1668)
  - Price, Ruth A., 1948 (Box 67, Folder 1669)
  - Prichett, Wilson, 1933-1943 (Box 67, Folder 1670)
  - Prochaska, A. Rudolph, 1940-1944 (Box 67, Folder 1671)
  - Procope, H. J., 1940-1948 (Box 67, Folder 1672)
  - Pryor, Samuel F., 1942-1956, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 1673)
  - Pulsifer, Susan N., 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 1674)
  - Pusta, Kaarel R., Jr., 1944-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1675)
  - Pusta, Kaarel R., Sr., 1944-1948 (Box 67, Folder 1676)
  - Q (Box 67, Folder 1677)
  - R-Re (Box 67, Folder 1678 - 1691)
  - Rh-Rz (Box 68, Folder 1692 - 1718)
  - R. H. Macy and Company, 1935-1943 (Box 69, Folder 1719)
  - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, 1939-1941 (Box 69, Folder 1720)
  - Radford, Arthur W., 1952-1956 (Box 69, Folder 1721)
  - Radford, Marianna, 1954-1956, undated (Box 69, Folder 1722)
  - Rankin, Karl L., 1952-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1723)
  - Rathaus, Rudolf, 1940-1943, 1947-1948, undated (Box 69, Folder 1724 - 1726)
  - Rawlins, H. Charles, 1942-1943 (Box 69, Folder 1727)
  - RCA, 1938-1943, undated (Box 69, Folder 1728 - 1730)
  - Reader's Digest, 1944-1953, 1961, undated (Box 69, Folder 1731 - 1734)
  - Reed, Charles, 1946-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1735)
  - Reed, Joseph V., 1938-1943, 1947-1955, undated (Box 69, Folder 1736 - 1738)
  - Reed, Permelia, 1938-1953 (Box 69, Folder 1739)
  - Refugees Defense Committee, 1947-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1740)
  - Reid, Helen, 1938-1948, undated (Box 69, Folder 1741)
  - Reignier, Emilienne and Félin, 1948-1953 (Box 69, Folder 1742)
  - Requin, [Edouard], 1937-1941 (Box 69, Folder 1743)
  - Reves, Emery, 1941-1942 (Box 69, Folder 1744)
  - Rey, Ainé, 1939 (Box 69, Folder 1745)
  - Reynaud, Paul, 1936-1941, undated (Box 69, Folder 1746)
  - Rhee, Syngman, 1941, 1953-1957, undated (Box 69, Folder 1747 - 1749)
  - Riesman, David, 1934-1940, undated (Box 69, Folder 1750 - 1751)
  - Riggs National Bank, 1942-1950 (Box 69, Folder 1752)
  - Rist, Charles, 1936-1939, undated (Box 69, Folder 1753)
  - Rittenhouse Club, 1917, 1934-1948, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1754)
  - Rivel, Thomas, 1939-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1755)
  - Robbins, Richard, 1911, 1933-1953, 1966-1967, undated (Box 70, Folder 1756 - 1764)
  - Robbins, William W., 1938-1943, undated (Box 70, Folder 1765)
  - Robert A. Taft Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1955 (Box 70, Folder 1766)
  - Robert, Evie, 1939-1942 (Box 70, Folder 1767)
  - Robert, Lawrence Wood, Jr., 1934-1942, undated (Box 70, Folder 1768)
  - Robinson, Adele, 1934-1940 (Box 70, Folder 1769 - 1770)
  - Robinson, Beverly, 1933-1934, 1938-1943, undated (Box 70, Folder 1771 - 1772)
  - Rogers, Walters, 1934-1935 (Box 70, Folder 1773)
  - Rogers, Will, 1934 (Box 70, Folder 1774)
  - Romains, Jules, 1940-1941 (Box 70, Folder 1775)
  - Roosevelt, Anne and John A., 1937-1939 (Box 70, Folder 1776)
  - Roosevelt, Belle W. and Kermit, 1934-1940, undated (Box 70, Folder 1777)
  - Roosevelt, Betsy, 1937-1940, undated (Box 70, Folder 1778)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1937-1945, 1954, undated (Box 70, Folder 1779)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1932-1933 (Box 70, Folder 1780 - 1782)
    See also: Series III. Writings, 1888-1984 Folder 453
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1934-1939 (Box 71, Folder 1783 - 1802)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1939-1941 (Box 72, Folder 1803 - 1821)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1942-1944, undated (Box 73, Folder 1822 - 1830)
  - Roosevelt, James, 1938-1940 (Box 73, Folder 1831)
  - Roosevelt, Sara Delano, 1937-1942, undated (Box 73, Folder 1832)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1916, 1937-1943, undated (Box 73, Folder 1833)
  - Roots, John McCook [includes photographs], 1935-1952, undated (Box 73, Folder 1834 - 1837)
  - Roots, Logan H., 1934-1940 (Box 73, Folder 1838)
  - Rosenberg, Rose, 1932-1939 (Box 73, Folder 1839)
  - Rosenfeld, Philip, 1909-1916, undated (Box 73, Folder 1840)
  - Rosenman, Samuel I., 1936-1952, undated (Box 73, Folder 1841)
  - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1948-1953 (Box 73, Folder 1842)
  - Rousseau, Theodore, 1938-1939 (Box 73, Folder 1843)
  - Rowe, L. S., 1935-1941 (Box 73, Folder 1844)
  - Rubinin, Evgéni Vladimirovitch, 1934 (Box 73, Folder 1845)
  - Rublee, Juliet Barrett, 1934-1946 (Box 73, Folder 1846)
  - Ryan, E. A. [includes photographs], 1940-1947 (Box 73, Folder 1847 - 1849)
  - Sac-Shi (Box 74, Folder 1850 - 1882)
  - Shl-Squ (Box 75, Folder 1883 - 1910)
  - Sta-Sz (Box 76, Folder 1911 - 1935)
  - Sack, A. J., 1947-1949 (Box 76, Folder 1936)
  - Sack, Leo R., 1933-1939 (Box 76, Folder 1937)
  - Sadoul, Jacques and Yvonne, 1935-1942 (Box 76, Folder 1938)
  - Safe Deposit and Trust Company, 1941-1944 (Box 76, Folder 1939)
  - Sah, Ben Y. and Margaret, 1949-1951 (Box 76, Folder 1940)
  - Saint Mary of the Springs College [The Erskine Lectures], 1946-1947 (Box 76, Folder 1941)
  - Sartori, Frank A., Jr., 1943 (Box 76, Folder 1942)
  - Sato, Michi, 1954-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1943)
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1942-1950 (Box 76, Folder 1944)
  - Saul, Walter Biddle, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 1945)
  - Sawyer, Philip, 1940 (Box 77, Folder 1946)
  - Scheffer, Paul, 1933-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1947)
  - Schenk, Harry P., 1938-1952 (Box 77, Folder 1948)
  - Scherbacher, Marcus W., 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 1949)
  - Scherbak, H., 1932-1949 (Box 77, Folder 1950 - 1951)
  - Schneider, John J., 1940-1941 (Box 77, Folder 1952)
  - Scholard, G. Joseph, 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1953)
  - Schranz, Hans, 1933-1936, undated (Box 77, Folder 1954)
  - Schwein, Edward [includes photographs], 1945-1953, undated (Box 77, Folder 1955 - 1956)
  - Scott, Hugh D., Jr., 1948-1950 (Box 77, Folder 1957)
  - Seaman, Mary, 1953-1955 (Box 77, Folder 1958)
  - Security Storage Company, 1933-1950, 1966, undated (Box 77, Folder 1959)
  - Seligman, George E., 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1960)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1926-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1961 - 1965)
  - Shah, Konsin C., 1950-1959, 1964-1967 (Box 77, Folder 1966 - 1968)
  - Shaw, G. Howland, 1936-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1969)
  - Shaw, Julie A. E., 1940 (Box 77, Folder 1970)
  - Shen, Sampson C., 1947-1956, undated (Box 77, Folder 1971 - 1973)
  - Sheperd, Lemuel C., Jr., 1948-1952 (Box 77, Folder 1974)
  - Sheronas, Victor F., 1934-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1975)
  - Shipley, Ruth B., 1937-1943 (Box 77, Folder 1976)
  - Shirer, William, 1933-1939 (Box 77, Folder 1977)
  - Shoop, Betty, 1934-1947, undated (Box 77, Folder 1978)
  - Shoop, Max, 1930-1950 (Box 78, Folder 1979 - 1982)
  - Sigmund Freud Archives, 1951-1954 (Box 78, Folder 1983)
  - Sigray, Anton, 1939-1947 (Box 78, Folder 1984)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1919-1920, 1941-1957, undated (Box 78, Folder 1985)
  - Skinner, Charles C., 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 1986)
  - Slater, Nelson, 1938 (Box 78, Folder 1987)
  - Smith, Alfred E. [includes photographs], 1934 (Box 78, Folder 1988)
  - Smith, Harold L., 1935-1944 (Box 78, Folder 1989 - 1990)
  - Smythe, David M., 1940-1943 (Box 78, Folder 1991)
  - Snell, John L., 1950-1953 (Box 78, Folder 1992)
  - Somlyo, Jeanne and Jeanette, 1944-1957 (Box 78, Folder 1993)
  - Soong, T. V., 1937-1947 (Box 78, Folder 1994)
  - Spellman, Francis J., 1939-1956 (Box 78, Folder 1995)
  - Spencer, DeForest, 1933-1942, 1948-1952, undated (Box 78, Folder 1996 - 1998)
  - Spencer, Frank E., 1946-1948 (Box 78, Folder 1999)
  - Speyer, James, 1933-1938 (Box 78, Folder 2000)
  - Spivak, Lawrence E. [includes photographs], 1945-1953 (Box 78, Folder 2001)
  - Spruance, Russell, 1933-1950 (Box 78, Folder 2002)
  - Spurgeon, John J., 1916-1918, undated (Box 78, Folder 2003)
  - Stafford, Alice Clyde, 1940-1941 (Box 78, Folder 2004)
  - Stanley, George C., 1933-1934 (Box 78, Folder 2005)
  - Stanwood, Charles F., 1940-1948, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 2006)
  - Stark, Harold R., 1942 (Box 78, Folder 2007)
  - Steen, J. Francis, 1940-1943 (Box 78, Folder 2008)
  - Steffens, Lincoln, 1923-1937 (Box 78, Folder 2009)
  - Steinhardt, Laurence, 1934-1941 (Box 78, Folder 2010)
  - Steinmetz, Philip Humason, 1945-1956 (Box 78, Folder 2011)
  - Sterling, Dorothy [includes photographs], 1938-1949 (Box 79, Folder 2012 - 2015)
  - Sterling, Frederick A., 1938-1941, undated (Box 79, Folder 2016)
  - Stern, Jules David, 1933-1943, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 2017 - 2018)
  - Stettinius, Edward R., 1940-1947 (Box 79, Folder 2019)
  - Stevens, Lewis M., 1943-1948 (Box 79, Folder 2020)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1940-1944 (Box 79, Folder 2021)
  - Stevenson, John A., 1941-1944 (Box 79, Folder 2022)
  - Steyne, Alan N., 1940-1944 (Box 79, Folder 2023)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1915, 1933-1944, undated (Box 79, Folder 2024)
  - Stokes, Edward Lowber, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 2025)
  - Stokes, Richard L., 1941-1951 (Box 79, Folder 2026)
  - Storrs, John H. and Marguerite, 1933-1940, undated (Box 79, Folder 2027)
  - Straus, Irma L., 1936-1944 (Box 79, Folder 2028 - 2029)
  - Straus, Jesse Isidor, 1933-1936 (Box 79, Folder 2030 - 2031)
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 1929-1965 (Box 79, Folder 2032)
  - Streit, Clarence K., 1929-1954, undated (Box 79, Folder 2033 - 2039)
  - Strohm, John Guy, 1944-1952 (Box 79, Folder 2040)
  - Stuart, Charles E., 1933-1939 (Box 80, Folder 2041 - 2042)
  - Sturges, Howard, 1939-1940 (Box 80, Folder 2043)
  - Sui Te-fu [includes photographs], 1959-1966 (Box 80, Folder 2044)
  - Sumner, Edward A., 1939-1946 (Box 80, Folder 2045)
  - Sun, C. H., 1953-1955 (Box 80, Folder 2046)
  - Sun Li-jen, 1952-1954, undated (Box 80, Folder 2047)
  - Sutherland, Millicent, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 2048)
  - Sweeney, Charles P., 1917-1920, undated (Box 80, Folder 2049)
  - Swei Der-fu, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 2050)
  - Swing, Raymond Gram, 1933-1940, undated (Box 80, Folder 2051)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1933-1943 (Box 80, Folder 2052 - 2053)
  - Ta-Tr (Box 80, Folder 2054 - 2067)
  - Ts-Ty (Box 81, Folder 2068 - 2070)
  - Tabouis, Genevieve, 1933-1954, undated (Box 81, Folder 2071 - 2072)
  - Taft, Robert A., 1941-1955 (Box 81, Folder 2073)
  - Taft committees, 1948-1952 (Box 81, Folder 2074)
  - Talbott, Katherine H. [includes photographs], 1933-1934 (Box 81, Folder 2075)
  - Talmey, Max, 1934 (Box 81, Folder 2076)
  - Tarnowski, Antoni, 1943-1954 (Box 81, Folder 2077)
  - Tate, Ben E., 1949-1952 (Box 81, Folder 2078)
  - Taylor, Anabel, 1937-1941 (Box 81, Folder 2079)
  - Taylor, Esther, 1934-1947 (Box 81, Folder 2080)
  - Taylor, Myron, 1937-1947 (Box 81, Folder 2081 - 2082)
  - Taylor, Roland L., 1941-1942 (Box 81, Folder 2083)
  - Taylor, Wayne Chattfield, 1938-1946 (Box 81, Folder 2084)
  - Taylor, William H., 1919, 1933-1941 (Box 81, Folder 2085)
  - Temple University, 1940-1941 (Box 81, Folder 2086)
  - Tetlow, Henry, 1933-1949 (Box 81, Folder 2087)
  - Thayer, Charles W., 1933-1953 (Box 81, Folder 2088)
  - Thayer, Elizabeth, 1938-1940 (Box 81, Folder 2089)
  - Thomas, Clara Fargo, 1934-1935 (Box 81, Folder 2090)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1919, 1937-1946 (Box 81, Folder 2091)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1940-1951, undated (Box 81, Folder 2092)
  - Thompson, Fellowes, 1934-1941 (Box 81, Folder 2093)
  - Thompson, John M. [includes drawing], 1953 (Box 81, Folder 2094)
  - Thompson, Kate, 1934- 1952 (Box 81, Folder 2095)
  - Thompson, Margaret B., 1943-1946 (Box 81, Folder 2096)
  - Thomson, James C., Jr., 1952 (Box 81, Folder 2097)
  - Thomson, Valentine, 1933-1950 (Box 81, Folder 2098)
  - Tilea, V. V., 1942 (Box 81, Folder 2099)
  - Time, Inc., 1942-1949, 1967, undated (Box 81, Folder 2100)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1915-1917, 1936-1949 (Box 82, Folder 2101)
  - Tinkham, George Holden, 1934-1953 (Box 82, Folder 2102)
  - Tisdale, Samuel P., 1954-1960 (Box 82, Folder 2103)
  - Tittman, Harold, 1933-1939 (Box 82, Folder 2104)
  - Tolces, Toska, 1939 (Box 82, Folder 2105)
  - Tong, Hollington "Holly", 1954-1958 (Box 82, Folder 2106)
  - Toretta, Marie Louise, 1942-1944 (Box 82, Folder 2107)
  - Torpats, John, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 2108)
  - Totten, George Oakley, Jr., 1933 (Box 82, Folder 2109)
  - Town Hall, Inc., 1947-1952 (Box 82, Folder 2110)
  - Townsend, Edward H., 1922-1941 (Box 82, Folder 2111)
  - Tran, William, 1960-1962, undated (Box 82, Folder 2112)
  - Trippe, Juan T., 1938-1952 (Box 82, Folder 2113)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1933 (Box 82, Folder 2114)
  - Troxelle, Grace Coleman, 1933 (Box 82, Folder 2115)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1944-1948 (Box 82, Folder 2116)
  - Trumble, Harold, 1960-1964, undated (Box 82, Folder 2117)
  - Tseng Tsze-lee [includes photographs], 1954-1967 (Box 82, Folder 2118 - 2121)
  - Tubelius, Vodre Jadvyga Anna, 1940-1949 (Box 82, Folder 2122)
  - Tuck, Edward, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 2123)
  - Tuck, S. Pinkney and Katherine [includes photographs], 1938-1957, undated (Box 82, Folder 2124 - 2125)
  - Tucker, Marguerite, 1933-1934 (Box 82, Folder 2126)
  - Tuckerman, Gustave, Jr., 1934 (Box 82, Folder 2127)
  - Tuczek, Nikolaus, 1920-1954 (Box 82, Folder 2128)
  - Tully, Grace, 1939-1946 (Box 82, Folder 2129)
  - Turner, Joseph A., 1933-1934 (Box 82, Folder 2130)
  - Tuttle, Joseph H., 1925-1936 (Box 82, Folder 2131)
  - Tyler, Royall, 1935-1950 (Box 82, Folder 2132)
  - U (Box 83, Folder 2133 - 2138)
  - United Charities Campaign, 1941-1942 (Box 83, Folder 2139)
  - United China Relief, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 83, Folder 2140 - 2142)
  - United Service to China, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 83, Folder 2143)
  - United States Air Force, Air War College, 1950-1952, undated (Box 83, Folder 2144)
  - United States Government Dispatch Agency, 1937-1940 (Box 83, Folder 2145)
  - United States Library of Congress, 1929, 1943-1967 (Box 83, Folder 2146)
  - United States Lines, 1933-1955 (Box 83, Folder 2147)
  - University Club of Washington, D.C., 1934, 1961-1965 (Box 83, Folder 2148)
  - Va-Ve (Box 83, Folder 2149 - 2151)
  - Vi-Vu (Box 84, Folder 2152 - 2154)
  - Vaccaro, Leopold S., 1943-1944 (Box 84, Folder 2155)
  - Valentin, François, 1938, 1954 (Box 84, Folder 2156)
  - Valentine, August J., 1947 (Box 84, Folder 2157)
  - Valyi, Felix, 1935-1942 (Box 84, Folder 2158)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, Jr., 1933-1944 (Box 84, Folder 2159)
  - Vanderherchen, William H., 1941-1947 (Box 84, Folder 2160)
  - Van Der Poel, A. "Gus", 1938-1939 (Box 84, Folder 2161)
  - Vanderschoot, Anthony C., 1938-1939 (Box 84, Folder 2162)
  - Van Duzer, William A., 1933 (Box 84, Folder 2163)
  - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem, 1936, 1941 (Box 84, Folder 2164)
  - Van Pelt, Andrew, 1938-1946, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 2165)
  - Van Voorhees, E. M., 1933-1938 (Box 84, Folder 2166)